<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Teaching on Felipe Valdez Gómez de la Torre</title>
    <link>https://felipevaldez.com/tags/teaching/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Teaching on Felipe Valdez Gómez de la Torre</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://felipevaldez.com/tags/teaching/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Ampliando la participación, creando comunidad y aprendiendo que nunca sale según lo planeado</title>
      <link>https://felipevaldez.com/paper2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://felipevaldez.com/paper2/</guid>
      <description>Este artículo discute un curso de aprendizaje-servicio que utilizó geografía comunitaria para evaluar un centro de investigación y comunitario propuesto en DeKalb, IL. A medida que los estudiantes interactuaban con las comunidades universitarias y locales, descubrimos preocupaciones e intereses compartidos, lo que llevó a análisis y recomendaciones colaborativas. El proyecto destaca la efectividad de la geografía comunitaria para fomentar discusiones significativas y abordar problemas compartidos, ofreciendo perspectivas para futuros estudios de relaciones entre la ciudad y la universidad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Broadening participation, creating community, and learning that it never goes as planned</title>
      <link>https://felipevaldez.com/paper2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://felipevaldez.com/paper2/</guid>
      <description>This paper discusses a service-learning course that used community geography to evaluate a proposed research and community center in DeKalb, IL. As students engaged with both university and local communities, we discovered shared concerns and interests, leading to collaborative analysis and recommendations. The project highlights the effectiveness of community geography in fostering meaningful discussions and addressing shared issues, offering insights for future town-gown relationship studies.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
